
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Recipes</string>
    <string name="lang_ru">Russian</string>
    <string name="lang_en">English</string>
    <string name="lang_es">Spanish</string>
    <string name="btn_lang">SELECT LANGUAGE</string>
    <string name="btn_filter_type">Filter by Type</string>
    <string name="btn_filter_name">Filter by Name</string>
    <string name="start_timer">Start Timer</string>
    <string name="end_timer">Stop</string>
    <string name="sec">sec.</string>
    <string name="remain">Remaining</string>
    <string name="steps">Steps: </string>
    <string name="bon_appetite">Bon Appétit!</string>
    <string name="start_receipt">Listen to Recipe</string>
    <string name="receipt_easy">Easy</string>
    <string name="receipt_mid">Medium</string>
    <string name="receipt_hard">Hard</string>
    <string name="ingidients">Ingredients</string>
    <string name="receipt_card_name">Name</string>
    <string name="receipt_card_time">Preparation Time</string>
    <string name="receipt_card_difficult">Difficulty</string>
    <string name="receipt_card_type">Dish Type</string>
    <string name="borcht_name">Borscht</string>
    <string name="borcht_time">5 hours</string>
    <string name="olady_name">Grandmas Pancakes</string>
    <string name="sirniks">Cottage Cheese Pancakes</string>
    <string name="deflope">Deflope made from palaba with kacius seeds</string>
    <string name="time_day">24 hours</string>
    <string name="time_half">30 minutes</string>
    <string name="type_soup">Soup</string>
    <string name="type_breakfast">Breakfast</string>
    <string name="type_delicates">Delicacy</string>
    <string name="difficult_easy">Easy</string>
    <string name="difficult_middle">Medium</string>
    <string name="difficult_hard">Hard</string>
    <string name="difficult_extra_hard">Very Hard</string>
    <string name="steps_for_sirnik">
    "1. In a large bowl, mix cottage cheese, eggs, sugar, vanilla extract (if using), and a pinch of salt. Mix well until smooth.\n" +
    "2. Gradually add wheat flour, continuing to mix, until the dough becomes thick and holds its shape.\n" +
    "3. Heat a frying pan with sunflower oil over medium heat.\n" +
    "4. Form small balls from the cottage cheese dough and slightly flatten them to resemble syrniki.\n" +
    "5. Roll each syrnik in a small amount of flour to prevent sticking to the pan and give the syrniki a tasty crust.\n" +
    "6. Place the syrniki on the heated frying pan and fry them for 2-3 minutes on each side until they become golden brown and cooked through.\n" +
    "7. After frying, place the cooked syrniki on a paper towel to remove excess oil.\n" +
    "8. Serve the syrniki hot, sprinkled with powdered sugar and with fresh fruits, berries, or jam as desired."
</string>

    <string name="ingridients_for_sirnik">
    "• 500 g cottage cheese (can use low-fat or medium-fat)\n" +
    "• 2 eggs\n" +
    "• 4 tablespoons sugar\n" +
    "• 1 teaspoon vanilla extract (optional)\n" +
    "• 3-4 tablespoons wheat flour\n" +
    "• Pinch of salt\n" +
    "• Sunflower oil for frying"
</string>

    <string name="ingridients_for_olady">
    "• 1 large egg\n" +
    "• 1 cup (about 200 ml) milk\n" +
    "• 1 cup (about 120-150 g) flour\n" +
    "• 2 tablespoons sugar\n" +
    "• 1 teaspoon baking powder\n" +
    "• Pinch of salt\n" +
    "• Sunflower oil for frying\n" +
    "• Optional additional ingredients: berries, sliced fruits, raisins, nuts, etc."
</string>

    <string name="steps_for_olady">
    "1. In a bowl, beat the egg with a fork or mixer until homogeneous.\n" +
    "2. Add milk and beat until well combined.\n" +
    "3. Gradually add flour, continuing to beat to avoid lumps.\n" +
    "4. Add sugar, baking powder, and a pinch of salt. Beat the batter until smooth and homogeneous.\n" +
    "5. Let the batter rest for 10-15 minutes to allow the flour to slightly swell.\n" +
    "6. Heat a frying pan over medium heat and add a little sunflower oil.\n" +
    "7. Pour a small amount of batter onto the pan to form pancakes of desired size (usually about 1/4 cup of batter per pancake).\n" +
    "8. Fry the pancakes on one side until bubbles appear on the surface and the bottom is golden brown, then flip them and fry on the other side.\n" +
    "9. Repeat the process with the remaining batter, adding sunflower oil to the pan as needed.\n" +
    "10. After frying, place the pancakes on a paper towel to remove excess oil.\n" +
    "11. Serve the pancakes hot with honey, syrup, fresh berries, fruits, or powdered sugar as desired."
</string>

    <string name="steps_for_deflope">
    "1. Prepare the palapa by peeling it and slicing it into thin slices.\n" +
    "2. In a deep bowl, beat eggs with a fork. Add milk, flour, sugar, vanilla extract, and a pinch of salt. Mix well until the batter is smooth without lumps.\n" +
    "3. Coat the slices of palapa in the batter to evenly cover them.\n" +
    "4. Heat a frying pan with sunflower oil over medium heat.\n" +
    "5. Fry the battered slices of palapa on both sides until golden brown and cooked through.\n" +
    "6. Once the palapa slices are ready, transfer them to a plate.\n" +
    "7. Sprinkle the cooked deflope with cashew seeds on top for added texture and flavor.\n" +
    "8. Serve the palapa deflope with cashew seeds hot as a main dish or dessert, sprinkled with powdered sugar and with fresh fruits or berries as desired."
</string>

    <string name="ingidients_for_deflope">
    "• 500 g palapa\n" +
    "• 100 g cashew seeds\n" +
    "• 2 eggs\n" +
    "• 100 ml milk\n" +
    "• 50 g flour\n" +
    "• 50 g sugar\n" +
    "• 1 tsp vanilla extract\n" +
    "• Pinch of salt\n" +
    "• Sunflower oil for frying"
</string>
    <string name="steps_for_borsht">
    "1. Cut the beef into medium-sized pieces. Put the meat in a large pot and cover with cold water so that the meat is completely submerged. Bring to a boil, then reduce the heat and simmer until the meat is tender (usually about 1-1.5 hours). Skim off any foam that forms on the surface of the pot. \n"
    "\n"
    "2. While the meat is cooking, prepare the vegetables. Peel and chop the beets, potatoes, onion, and carrots. Also, chop the cabbage and finely chop the garlic.\n"
    "3. When the meat is almost done, add the chopped beets and potatoes to the pot. Cook until the vegetables are tender.\n"
    "4. In a separate skillet, sauté the chopped onion and carrots until soft and golden brown. Add the tomato paste and sauté for a few more minutes.\n"
    "5. Add the sautéed onion and carrots to the pot with the broth and vegetables. Also, add the chopped cabbage and garlic.\n"
    "6. Continue to simmer the borscht over medium heat for another 10-15 minutes to allow all the flavors to combine.\n"
    "7. Then add salt, pepper, and vinegar to taste. Adjust the amount of vinegar according to your preference.\n"
    "8. Serve the borscht hot, garnished with sour cream and fresh herbs if desired. Borscht is usually served with black bread or dumplings.\n"
</string>
    <string name="ingridients_for_bosht">
    "• 500g beef\n"
            "• 2-3 large beets\n"
            "• 2-3 medium potatoes\n"
            "• 1 large onion\n"
            "• 1-2 carrots\n"
            "• 1/4 cabbage\n"
            "• 2-3 cloves of garlic\n"
            "• 2-3 tablespoons of tomato paste\n"
            "• 2-3 bay leaves\n"
            "• Salt and pepper to taste\n"
            "• Vinegar to taste\n"
            "• Sour cream and herbs for serving"
</string>
</resources>